Shalom Odozi

 ♥ Flat 10 Paris corte, 75 Loampit vale, SE13 7FN, United Kingdom
 ■ shalomodozi7@gmail.com

**** 07572592505

Profile

I am a highly motivated and forward-thinking graduate who is eager to learn. My science degree has given me confidence to work with large amount of data and become very analytical and critical in my thinking. I have a passion for technology so I started teaching myself python. From there my work experience has introduced me to several other technologies such as Java, mySQL and different forms of testing including automation and manual. I continue to learn HTML, CSS and JavaScript and Docker. With almost 4 years experience in the hospitality sector I can provide outstanding customer service which means I can relate well with clients. work in fast paced environment and I can keep up with demand. I am seeking an opportunity to utilise my transferable skills learnt from my science degree and my work experience in an outstanding company

Skills		
• Java	• CSS3	• HTML5
• SQL	• Docker	 Selenium webdriver
• Cucumber	Gherkin	Python

Professional Experience

04/2020 - present

Ten10

Graduate trainee/Junior consultant

- Worked well in teams on several projects, completing test scripts, test sessions, finding bugs and logging it in JIRA.
- Completed a small project using SQL.
- Tested websites using selenium webdriver and Java, Cucumber and Gherkin.
- Used Agile methodologies when completing projects
- Learnt Java and used it to create several games and in Test automation.
- Looked into web development and created a practice website.

06/2016 - 02/2020

Urban people, Harris & Porter recruitment, High society (hospitality agencies) *Bar staff, Waiting and Cashier*

- I provided excellent customer service at various events and venues including Weddings, Stadiums and Festivals.
- Worked in teams to provide simultaneous food and drink service.
- Counted stock before and after a shift for inventory management
- Replenished stock throughout shifts.
- Used the till system to complete transactions
- Dealt with customer enquiries and progressed it to the Manager when necessary
- I represented my agencies very well, by showing good communication, initiative, punctuality and teamwork. Clients have requested to work with me again.

07/2018 - 08/2018

London interdisciplinary doctoral programme with Doctor Sula at Birbeck college

Intern

- I assisted Dr Sula with a range of experiments and learned different experimental techniques
- I processed and analysed large amounts of data generated in order to identify the target subject
- Interpreted the data in order to present the findings to colleagues and fellow academics so it was understandable to the public.
- I was able to follow instructions and use my own initiative in certain experiments to give a better outcome.

Education

09/2016 - 05/2019

University of Hertfordshire

Pharmacology

Key modules include pharmacology, bioscience and research methods.

Transferable skills learnt:

- Analytical: Performed a range of experiments and analysed the data to produce lab reports and wrote a literature review on potassium channels.
- Worked with large amounts of complex data in my dissertation, where I organised, interpreted and presented the data so it was easy to understand.
- Teamwork/Presentation: Presented a range of assignments from scientific posters from scientific posters to clinical stimulation where we received high grades.
- Time management: Managed my time with assignment deadlines, coordinating group works and exam revisions.

2014 - 2016

Chislehurt and Sidcup grammar school

A-Levels studied- Biology, Chemistry and History

2009 - 2014

Eltham Hill School

Obtained 11 A* to Cs in GCSE's

Interests

Reading

Crochet

• Gym

· Watching documentaries.